Lloyd: Now that you've completed
session one, of unit two, it's
time to complete the relevant
section in the assessment booklet.
If you haven't already done so
you can download the assessment by
clicking on the assessment link and
then downloading and saving that in
a suitable location on your computer.
Once you've done that, you
can then open the unit two
assessment booklet, and begin.
As you will see, as with assessment
one, the assessment guidance is at
the top, giving you an outline of the
way you should answer your questions
depending on whether it's describe,
explain, identify, list, and so on.
And then if you scroll down to page
two pop, your name at the top, we have
section one: Understand Cyber Security
Terminology, and there are four learning
outcomes in this section and the place in
the assessment, and also the location of
the information in the course materials
should you wish to refresh your memory.
So for question 1, it's asking you to
define what is meant by the following
in relation to cyber security: hardware,
software, data management and networking.
I strongly suggest you take note of
the key points here, where you must
include a definition of operating
system software and applications
software in your answer to this.
Similar for data management, you must
include confidentiality, integrity,
and accessibility in your answer.
And for networking, you must
include the definitions of LAN,
WAN and MAN in your response.
So again, give a definition of
what is meant by all of those
in relation to cyber security.
For question 2, it's asking
you to describe the differences
between a LAN and a WAN.
So what is a LAN?
What is a WAN?
What is different about those?
And for question 3, it's asking
you to explain the following terms
in relation to cyber security:
So what is a vulnerability?
What is a risk?
What is an attack?
What is protection?
And what is recovery in
relation to cyber security?
For 3B, it's asking you to explain
the following types of threat
in relation to cyber security.
So what do these types of
threat mean in relation to that?
So what is a denial of service attack?
What is a DDoS attack -- a
distributed denial of service attack?
What is botnet software?
What is a Trojan?
What is ransomware?
Spyware?
And viruses?
So again, try and provide as
much detail in your responses
because it is an explain question.
And for question four, it's asking you
to describe organisational strategies
in relation to cyber security.
So if you look back on the course
materials, what is a sock and what is
a knock and what are they in relation
to organisational strategies to protect
themselves in relation to cyber security.
Once you've done that, you can
check through your answers, make
sure that you're happy with them
and see if the assessment booklet
and move on to session two.